<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blue on Hello w3nch</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/blue/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blue on Hello w3nch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/blue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LetsDefend SOC138 – Suspicious XLS Malware Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc138---detected-suspicious-xls-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc138---detected-suspicious-xls-file/</guid>
      <description>Alert Name: SOC138 – Detected Suspicious Xls File&#xA;Severity: High&#xA;Event ID: 77&#xA;Event Time: Mar 13, 2021, 08:20 PM&#xA;Category: Malware&#xA;Play Book 1. Alert Overview A high-risk malware alert was triggered due to the detection of a suspicious Excel macro-enabled file (.xlsm) on the host Sofia. Macro-enabled Excel documents are commonly abused to deliver malware via embedded VBA code that downloads and executes malicious payloads.&#xA;The file was allowed by the security device, increasing the potential risk of system compromise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LetsDefend SOC168 – Command Injection (whoami) Web Attack Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc168---whoami-command-detected-in-request-body/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc168---whoami-command-detected-in-request-body/</guid>
      <description>Alert Name: SOC168 – Whoami Command Detected in Request Body&#xA;Severity: High&#xA;Event ID: 118&#xA;Event Time: Feb 28, 2022, 04:12 AM&#xA;Category: Web Attack&#xA;Play Book 1. Alert Overview A high-severity web attack alert was triggered on WebServer1004 due to the detection of the whoami command within the HTTP request body. This behavior is commonly associated with command injection attempts, where an attacker tries to execute system-level commands through a web application.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LetsDefend SOC170 – Local File Inclusion (LFI) Attempt Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc170---passwd-found-in-requested-url---possible-lfi-attack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc170---passwd-found-in-requested-url---possible-lfi-attack/</guid>
      <description>Field Value Event ID 120 Event Time Mar 01, 2022, 10:10 AM Rule SOC170 – Passwd Found in Requested URL – Possible LFI Attack Analyst Level Security Analyst Hostname WebServer1006 Destination IP Address 172.16.17.13 Source IP Address 106.55.45.162 HTTP Request Method GET Requested URL https://172.16.17.13/?file=../../../../etc/passwd User-Agent Mozilla/4.0 (compatible; MSIE 6.0; Windows NT 5.1; .NET CLR 1.1.4322) Alert Trigger Reason URL contains passwd Device Action Allowed Play Book 1. Alert Overview A web attack alert was triggered on WebServer1006 due to the detection of a directory traversal payload attempting to access the sensitive system file /etc/passwd via an HTTP GET request.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LetsDefend SOC335 – CVE-2024-49138 Privilege Escalation Exploitation Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/-soc335--cve-2024-49138-privilege-escalation-exploitation-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/-soc335--cve-2024-49138-privilege-escalation-exploitation-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Alert Name: SOC335 – CVE-2024-49138 Exploitation Detected&#xA;Severity: High&#xA;Event ID: 313&#xA;Event Time: Jan 22, 2025, 02:37 AM&#xA;Category: Privilege Escalation&#xA;Base Information Field Value Event ID 313 Event Time Jan 22, 2025, 02:37 AM Rule SOC335 – CVE-2024-49138 Exploitation Detected Analyst Level Security Analyst Hostname Victor IP Address 172.16.17.207 Process Name svohost.exe Process Path C:\temp\service_installer\svohost.exe Process ID 7640 Parent Process C:\Windows\System32\WindowsPowerShell\v1.0\powershell.exe Command Line ??\C:\Windows\system32\conhost.exe 0xffffffff -ForceV1 File Hash (SHA-256) b432dcf4a0f0b601b1d79848467137a5e25cab5a0b7b1224be9d3b6540122db9 Process User EC2AMAZ-ILGVOIN\LetsDefend Trigger Reason Suspicious behavior patterns linked to CVE-2024-49138 Device Action Allowed Incident Details Field Value Incident Name EventID 313 – SOC335 CVE-2024-49138 Exploitation Incident Type Privilege Escalation Created Date Jan 08, 2026, 09:12 AM Pre-Investigation Notes Date: Jan 22, 2025, 02:37 AM Hostname: Victor IP Address: 172.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
