<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Powershell on Hello w3nch</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/powershell/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Powershell on Hello w3nch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/powershell/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SOC153 Case Study: Malicious PowerShell Execution Leading to Active Malware Infection</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc153---suspicious-powershell-script-executedname/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc153---suspicious-powershell-script-executedname/</guid>
      <description>#soc #letsdefend&#xA;Event ID: 238&#xA;Rule Name: SOC153 – Suspicious PowerShell Script Executed&#xA;Severity: HIGH&#xA;Category: Endpoint Compromise / Malware&#xA;Event Time: March 14, 2024 – 05:23 PM&#xA;Compromised Host: Tony (172.16.17.206)&#xA;Someone at work opened a suspicious file they probably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have. It was like finding a strange USB drive in the parking lot and plugging it into your computer you don&amp;rsquo;t know what&amp;rsquo;s on it, but it starts doing things automatically.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOC205 Case Study: Malicious Macro Execution via Phishing Invoice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc205---malicious-macro-has-been-executed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc205---malicious-macro-has-been-executed/</guid>
      <description>Alert Name: SOC205 – Malicious Macro has been executed&#xA;Severity: High&#xA;Event ID: 231&#xA;Event Time: Feb 28, 2024 – 08:42 AM&#xA;Category: Malware&#xA;Platform: LetsDefend SOC&#xA;Executive Summary (Management / Business) On February 28, 2024, a user received a malicious email that appeared to contain a legitimate invoice document. When the user opened the attachment, hidden malicious code inside the document was automatically executed.&#xA;This hidden code attempted to connect to an external system controlled by an attacker and download additional harmful software.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LetsDefend SOC138 – Suspicious XLS Malware Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc138---detected-suspicious-xls-file/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/letsdefend/alerts/soc138---detected-suspicious-xls-file/</guid>
      <description>Alert Name: SOC138 – Detected Suspicious Xls File&#xA;Severity: High&#xA;Event ID: 77&#xA;Event Time: Mar 13, 2021, 08:20 PM&#xA;Category: Malware&#xA;Play Book 1. Alert Overview A high-risk malware alert was triggered due to the detection of a suspicious Excel macro-enabled file (.xlsm) on the host Sofia. Macro-enabled Excel documents are commonly abused to deliver malware via embedded VBA code that downloads and executes malicious payloads.&#xA;The file was allowed by the security device, increasing the potential risk of system compromise.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GothamLegend Incident Response – PowerShell Malware Analysis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/writeups/btlo/security-operations/gothamlegend-incident-response--powershell-malware-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/writeups/btlo/security-operations/gothamlegend-incident-response--powershell-malware-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Scenario&#xA;Recently the networks of a large company named GothamLegend were compromised after an employee opened a phishing email containing malware. The damage caused was critical and resulted in business-wide disruption. GothamLegend had to reach out to a third-party incident response team to assist with the investigation. You are a member of the IR team - all you have is an encoded Powershell script. Can you decode it and identify what malware is responsible for this attack?</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
